Contact

Kochampil House Cheroor POST Evannur Thrissur 9496839168 (Home) jibintcr@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jibintcr (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Lecturing
Educational Leadership
Digital Forensics

Certifications

Networking Basics
Introduction to IoT
Certified Blockchain Associate
Managing Your Emotions at Work
Creativity at Work: A Short Course
from Seth Godin

JIBIN N

Founder Infinio Technologies | Educator-BITS Pilani | Oracle Academy Educator | Trailhead Educator | Nodal officer-KSUM IEDC Thrissur, Kerala, India

Summary

Experienced Assistant Professor with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Lecturing, Educational Technology, Instructional Design, Management, and Science. Strong education professional with a Master of Technology, M-Tech focused in Computer Science and Engineering from Ponnaiyah Ramajayam Institute of Science & Technology, Thanjavur.

Experience

MES College Marampally, Ernakulam Faculty
November 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Birla Institute of Technology and Science, Pilani Adjunct Faculty February 2016 - Present (7 years 11 months)

Kerala Startup Mission Nodal Officer KSUM IEDC December 2015 - August 2022 (6 years 9 months) Kochi, Kerala, India

MES ADVANCED INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT AND TECHNOLOGY

Assistant Professor December 2015 - July 2022 (6 years 8 months) Aluva

Cochin University of Science and Technology Assistant Professor May 2015 - December 2016 (1 year 8 months) Kochi

Education

Karpagam Academy of Higher Education

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Cyber Forensics · (2019)

Ponnaiyah Ramajayam Institute of Science & Technology, Thanjavur Master of Technology - MTech, Computer Science · (2012 - 2014)

COLLEGE OF APPLIED SCIENCES, VADAKKANCHERY Master of Computer Applications - MCA · (2007 - 2010)

St. Thomas' College (Autonomous), Thrissur BSc - Bachelor of Science, physics · (June 2004 - May 2007)